For my design, I used two primary data structures to ensure ease of use and proper runtimes. The
first was the MinPQ provided by the author with slight modifications. This implementation of the 
priority queue uses a binary heap to back the queue. The other data structure I used was a Hashmap.
This is the standard Hashmap developed for the Java libraries. The main use of these data structures
in CarList.java. CarTracker.java is simply the menu options, CarData.java represents a car and it's 
data, and the MinPQ.java is the modified priority queue provided by the author of the book.

Both the Hashmaps and MinPQ require N amount of space to store their data. I used two Hashmaps
that do not hold the same references, so a that's 2N space, and two MinPQ that hold the same references,
so only N space there. Therefore, my total space required is O(3N), which is just O(N) asymptotically.

The runtimes for the Hashmap are as follows:
 + insert - Θ(1)
 + find - Θ(1)
 + delete - Θ(1)
 These are the runtimes we discussed in lecture, and are enforced by the standard Java libraries.
 The only difference is that in the worst case, inserting is O(log n) because the Java Hashmap
 is structured more like a tree. This runtime will most likely never be reached, however, because 
 I don't anticipate the testers inputting hundreds of new cars to the collection.

The runtimes for the MinPQ are as follows:
 + finding the min - Θ(1)
 + deleting the min - Θ(log n)
 + inserting - Θ(log n)
 + updating a value - Θ(log n)
 These are the runtimes we discussed in lecture, and are enforced by the author's code, even with
 my own modifications to their code. We did not discuss updating, but I will explain why it is
 Θ(log n). Because the queue is indexable, looking for some value is Θ(1) due to the Hashmap's
 find() runtime. Changing the values of a car will always be constant Because it is just an update.
 After values are updated, the heap structure may be compromised, so the heap will need to be restructured.
 As we discussed in lecture, doing so will have a worst case runtime of O(log n). Therefore, 
 updating a value has a runtime of Θ(1) + O(log n) which is simply Θ(log n).

The biggest reason I used a Hashmap as my indirection was for the Θ(1) runtimes. Realistically, 
it is impossible to store N data in less than O(N) space, so that was not an issue when picking 
the Hashmap. The direct access retrievals given some key (the VIN in this problem) made searching,
updating, and removing much more efficient than another data structure. Additionally, the code 
is already tested, debugged, and optimized by Sun Microsystems, so it made sense to use their 
version rather than trying to create my own.

The biggest reason I used a priority queue was because we were continually required to find the minimum
of a collection of data. This is the very basis of what makes a MinPQ successfully in this situation.
Again, as with a Hashmap, it is impossible to store N items in less than N space, so space was not
an issue when choosing this data structure. All of the required operations were either constant
or logarithmic runtimes as well, so this way I could not violate the condition that all operations
must be of Θ(log n) or better. As with the Java Hashmap, the code the author provides is already
an acceptable implementation of a MinPQ, so there was no reason to create my own. 

In summary, neither data structure exceeds O(N) space to store the collection, so that right off the
bat is a huge advantage they provide over other data structures. Additionally, using the Hashmap
to make the MinPQ indexable adds no overhead to the programs runtime. By this statement, I mean that
because the Hashmap provides constant runtimes across the board in the average case, I did not have
to worry about optimizing the MinPQ in anyway. This is most prominent reason I chose a Hashmap over 
similar mapping data structures. Since the MinPQ is backed by a binary heap, all of my required
methods will take no more than Θ(log n) in the average case. Again, this is a huge advantage considering
finding the min of the collection is the basis of this project. Making the MinPQ backed by a binary 
heap and indexable by a Hashmap, I guaranteed that my space requirement will never exceed O(n), and
my overall runtime on any operation will never exceed Θ(log n) in the average cases. 